(Sheldon:)No, go ahead, say it.
(Sheldon:)I know what it is.
I've heard it my whole life.
The word's "annoying".
Go ahead, say it.
(Sheldon:)Say it. Say I'm annoying.
(Sheldon:)-Sheldon...
-Oh, it won't hurt my feelings.
(Sheldon:)Go ahead, Amy, say I'm annoying.
(Sheldon:)I'm annoying. I'm annoying.
(Sheldon:)I'm annoying.
Yeah, now where are you going?
(Sheldon:)Look, you know you want
to say it. Say it.
(Sheldon:)Say I'm annoying. Go ahead, say it.
(Sheldon:)Say it. Say it. Amy, say it.
(Sheldon:)Well, she can't stand it
when I'm right.
(Amy:)This is fun.
(Amy:)I'm going to feel like such
a vixen wearing jewelry
(Amy:)that doesn't have a list
of medications I'm allergic to.
(Raj:)Penny, how's it going over there?
(Penny:)Good. I'm just having
little trouble with the glue.
(Amy:)How do you not know how to use glue?
Did you ditch pre-school?
(Penny:)Yeah, but only because
I was dating a second grader.
(Howard:)Hello, everyone.
(Raj:)Okay, let me have it.